[
  {
    "question": "What is Blockchain?",
    "answer": "Ledger"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Arweave mainly offer?",
    "answer": "Storage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which programming language is commonly used for Ethereum smart contracts?",
    "answer": "Solidity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of a cryptographic hash function in blockchain technology?",
    "answer": "Integrity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'DAO' stand for in blockchain terminology?",
    "answer": "Organization"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Arweave differ from traditional blockchain storage solutions?",
    "answer": "Access"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'Gas' in the context of Ethereum?",
    "answer": "Fee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which consensus algorithm does Bitcoin use?",
    "answer": "Work"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an NFT?",
    "answer": "Token"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Arweave, what is the term for the fee paid by users to store data?",
    "answer": "Endowment"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key feature of the blockweave structure used by Arweave?",
    "answer": "Link"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a 'Smart Contract'?",
    "answer": "Contract"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which technology is a fundamental component of cryptocurrencies?",
    "answer": "Blockchain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'sharding' in blockchain?",
    "answer": "Scalability"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the context of Arweave, what is 'permaweb'?",
    "answer": "Hosting"
  }
]
